我东西都收拾好了么 Gary?  是的 我们东西都齐了
- Am I all packed, Gary? - Yeah, we're all covered.
俄亥俄的天气太你妈精神分裂了 -
The thing about Ohio is the weather is completely schizophrenic.
我明白 如果给你穿错了衣服的话
I know.  We dress you wrong,
那你不是冻得像根冰棍就是热得像条狗
you're either freezing like a popsicle or you're sweating like a hog.
或者说是像跳芭蕾舞或者现代舞的  好了 没关系的
Or a ballerina or modern dancer.  Okay, it's fine.
这个地方有室内泳池么? 我带了游泳裤
Is there an indoor pool at this place? I packed my swimsuit.
你为什么问我这个? 还有我们有总统那边的消息吗?
Why are you asking me that? And have we heard from the president
在经济论坛？
on the economic forum?
噢 有的 我才听说他打了高于标准杆三杆的成绩
Uh, yeah. Last I heard, he was three over par.
哈?  噢 论坛取消了
Huh?  Oh, forum's not happening.
总统去打高尔夫去了 -
Potus took a golf day.
你知道是谁和他一起去的么?
Do you know who he's playing golf with?
不知道 谁啊?  不 不 不 是谁?
No, who?  No, no, no, who?
噢 是你不知道然后让我去打听
Oh, you don't know and you want me to find out.
是的  好的 对不起
Yeah, yeah.  Okay. Sorry.
Dan Dan Egan  嘿
Dan. Dan Egan.  Hey.
很高兴见到你啊 哥们 我可想你的邮件了
Good to see you again, buddy. I miss your emails.
好久不抄件了啊 -
Long time no cc.
你还在克利夫兰哈 Will?
Still up here in Cleveland, huh, Will?
你就在地方的猪圈里滚么?
Just rutting around with the regional swine?
为Furlong当牛做马? -
Slaving away for Furlong?
呃 我现在是资深顾问了
Well, I am the senior advisor now.
所以我可以有免费无线网 还能经常去华盛顿
So I get free wi-fi. I'll be going to D.C. a lot more.
我的天啊 凭着你州级的政治敏感度
Oh, my God. With that provincial sensibility
还有这副娘味的样子 你是混不了多久的
and that girlish figure, you're not gonna last.
听着 Dan 众议员希望你的老板为他竞选州长背书
Listen, Dan, the congressman expects your boss to endorse him for governor.
是的 我们知道这个事 -
Yeah, we're aware of that.
事情有点复杂 好吗?
It's gotten a bit complex, all right?
所以众议员要和你在房间里谈谈
So the congressman would like to speak with you in his room.
跟我来 好吗?
If you'd just join me, okay?
啊 我认出你来了 你是Selina身边的小基人儿 对吧?
Ah, I recognize you. You're one of Selina's little gay dwarves, aren't you?
你是叫傻皮么? 还是嫩皮?  其实我的名字叫 Dan Egan
What, are you sappy? Is that it? Preppy?
你可能记得 事实上我曾经为Hayes众议员工作过
Actually, my name is Dan Egan.
天哪 我当然不记得了
You might remember, actually, I used to work for congresswoman Hayes.
听着 我需要你的帮助 哥们 我需要你回去告诉Selina
Oh, my gosh, of course I don't remember that.
说我不要她给我参选州长背书了 好吗?
Listen, I need your help, buddy. I need you to go back and tell Selina
她现在就和洗澡盆里的粑粑一样不招人待见
that I don't want her to endorse me for governor, okay?
呃 这可能有点问题
She's about as welcome here as a turd in a hot tub.
我们办的是筹款会 而她就是票房毒药 好吗?
Well, that could be a bit of an issue.
我们要把银盘子升级到金盘子
We're trying to run a fundraiser and she's kind of
金盘子要升级到铂金盘子
gold plates are going up to platinum plates.
我把Will装在乔治城的同志吧门口
I'd make more money if I installed Will here
作全天候欢迎菊挣的钱都比这个多
as a full-time glory hole greeter at a Georgetown gay bar.
我十分肯定他已经在兼职干这个了
Which I'm pretty sure he already does part-time.
对吧 Will?  是的 先生
Right, Will?  Yes, sir.
众议员先生 她现在已经在来这里的路上了
Congressman, she's on her way here right now.
那又怎么样? 在克利夫兰有大把事情可以做啊
So what? There's plenty to do here in Cleveland.
带她去摇滚名人堂好了
Send her to the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
我第一次带这孩子去的时候
First time I took this kid,
他看了一眼Kurt Cobain的鞋就他妈疯狂了 (摇滚巨星 27岁去世)
one look at Kurt Cobain's shoes, he was bawling like a fucking baby.
英年早逝啊!英年早逝啊!
It's too soon! It's too soon!
女士 Martin Collins 就是那个被我们调走的特勤处的人...
Ma'am, Martin Collins, the secret service guy we reassigned...
嗯哼  他回来了 他被反调了
Mm-hmm.  He's back. He's been un-reassigned.
你玩我呢吧?  情况确实不咋地
Are you kidding me?  Not great, admittedly.
确实不咋地? 对 这个就他妈应该是我回忆录的标题
Not great, admittedly? Yeah, that should be the title of my fucking memoir.
他不是就在门口吧 是吗? 噢 嗨...
He's not outside here, is he? Oh, hi!
我的个...! 好的 很好
Oh, my! Okay, great.
好吧 那是我这辈子愿意和他说的最后一句话了
All right, that's all I want to say to him for the rest of my life.
嘿 支持率出来了
Hey, approval ratings just came through.
Oh.  66%.
什么?  支持
What?  Approve.
噢!  对不起 是不支持
Oh!  Sorry, disapprove.
噢  不...
Oh.  Dis...
你知道吗? 你去和安保人员一块坐去
You know what? You go ride with the security detail.
这车里没你的地儿了
There's no room for you in this car.
她可以感谢军队啊
She can thank the troops,
她可以去迷倒随便什么二货
she can charm all the mouth-breathers,
她还可以回华盛顿嘛 没啥大不了的
and then she can go back to D.C. No big deal.
她唯一不会做的事就是
The one thing she will not be doing
站出来为我背书 你懂了吗?
is standing up and endorsing me. You got me?
如果我得到了她的支持的话
I get the stamp of approval from her,
那我就可能就得去找些狗崽来按到地上
and I might as well nail a bunch of puppies to the ground
然后用我的竞选大巴去压死它们 碾碎它们的脑袋
and then start running them over and crush their skulls with my campaign bus.
没有冒犯的意思 我们之前是...
All due respect, we did have a...
达成了一个非正式的协议 要她来支持你竞选州长
informal understanding that she would endorse your run for governor.
好吧 没有冒犯的意思 傻逼
All right, well, all due respect, cock nugget,
现在这个非正式的协议
there's been a little too much of this
有点太萦绕不去了
informal understanding going on around here.
对吧 Will?  是的 先生
Isn't that right, Will?  Yes, sir.
绿色产业是你们办公室出品的吧?
Clean jobs was your office, right?
还有它在Macauley修正案里的角色
And its role in the Macauley amendment.
让Macauley参议员违背总统意愿
Getting Senator Macauley to sneak in the VP's
去偷偷提交副总统糟糕的法案
lame-ass legislation against the president's will.
Macauley事件 那没有发生过
Macauley thing, yeah, that didn't happen.
Will 告诉他我是谁
Will, tell him who I am.
先生 你是国会监督委员会的副主席
Sir, you're the vice chair of the congressional oversight committee.
而拥有这样的能力就意味着我有义务
And in that capacity, I have a duty to shine a light
去曝光这种肮脏的幕后玩意 Dan
on any of this kind of backseat, finger-fucking insider bullshit, Dan.
谢谢你花了这么多时间 众议员
Thank you for your time, congressman.
我会尽力而为的
I will do what I can.
不许背书
Don't endorse.
她看起来挺好的
She seems nice.
就因为那个笑面特勤人员 Amy
'Cause of that smiling secret service guy, Amy,
66%的人不支持啊
66% disapprove.
现在全美国也就这么多人醒着
That's everyone in America who's awake right now.
好吧 我们今天先不要关心那个
Okay, let's not concentrate on that today.
我们要集中精神在俄亥俄州
Let's concentrate on Ohio.
怎么可能有这么多美国人不喜欢我?
How could that many Americans not like me?
我觉得他们搞错了 他们数错了数什么之类的
I think they got it wrong. They counted those numbers wrong or something.
要不就是所有那些美国人都错了
Or all those Americans are completely wrong.
好了 这是酒店经理 我们答应他可以有四秒钟
Okay, this is the hotel manager. We promised him four seconds.
副总统女士 欢迎来到我们酒店
Madam Vice President. Welcome to our hotel.
我们得把副总统带走了 很抱歉
We have to take the vice president away. Apologies.
为什么要给我这杯猪血?
Why have I been given this pig's blood?
那是番茄汁 是俄亥俄的招牌饮品
It's tomato juice. It's the Ohio state beverage.
我去 呃...女士  什么?
Oh, piss. Ma'am.  Yeah?
他们那个大额捐款的票卖不出去
They're having trouble moving big donor tickets.
什么?  是的
What?  Yeah.
为什么? 因为我吗?  不是的
Why? Because of me?  No.
Amy 你得着手让大家都喜欢我
Amy, you're gonna have to start getting everyone to like me.
女士 有好消息
Ma'am. Hi. Good news.
我们没有卖出去太多铂金票 -
We are not exactly selling that many platinum level tickets.
我已经说过了
I just gave her that news.
但是后面的这条消息会更让你郁闷的
Yeah, but it was so much more depressing coming out of you.
别担心 我有对策
Not to worry. I have a strategy.
好了 听着 我们该笑笑 该握手握手
Okay, look, we smile the smiles, we shake the hands,
但是我们不能背书 我们不让媒体有材料报道
but we do not endorse. We give the press nothing to report.
不 那样显得我更弱了
No, that makes me look even weaker.
好吧 女士 我...  嘿
All right, ma'am, I...  Hey.
我真觉得这事值得考虑
I really think this is something to consider.
Jonah.
这是来自权力俱乐部的问候 Amy
Greetings from the clubhouse of power, Amy.
你要知道 白宫明白最近的民意调查数字
You need to know that the White House understands
意味着副总统有多毒
just how toxic the veep is after these latest numbers.
这是道难关 我们知道
It's a tough time, we're aware.
你想知道她毒性有多强么 Amy?
Do you want to know how toxic she is, Amy?
你想象一下从死牛屁眼里爬出来的小东西
Imagine something small has crawled up a dead cow's ass.
然后这个小东西还死了
And then that small thing actually dies itself.
这个死掉的小玩意还放了一堆蛋出来
If that dead thing then farted out a sack of eggs,
而这每一个蛋里
but each individual egg
都有一个更小的烂了的死东西
is a smaller, rotting dead thing,
她现在就有这么毒
that's how toxic she is.
好了 谢谢你的资讯
Okay, thanks for the input.
而且我知道你现在压力很大
And I know you're under a lot of pressure over there,
如果你需要个肩膀靠着哭或者是要约炮什么的
so if you ever need a shoulder to cry on
你有我电话的哈...
or a booty to call on, you have my number...
你知道总统是和谁打高尔夫了么?
Did you find out who the president's playing golf with?
高尔夫 就是男人们带着棍子到处走
Golf. You know, men walking around with sticks
然后谈论事业的那个东西  噢
talking about their careers.  Oh, mm.
我本来是要跟进的 女士 我没有忘记的
I was gonna follow up on that, ma'am. I didn't forget.
我没有忘记
I did not forget.
女士 是Furlong众议员
Ma'am, it's congressman Furlong.
呃你可以告诉他去操自己...  他已经来了 女士
Well, you can tell him to go fuck him...  He's right here, ma'am.
噢 Roger  副总统女士
Oh!Roger.  Madam Vice President.
非常感谢你能见我 -
Thank you so much for seeing me.
谢谢你能来
Well, thank you for dropping by.
不好意思我要整理一下
Excuse me while I get myself pulled together.
当然 我很喜欢这个房间 这非常棒
Of course. I like this room. This is great.
对啊 这是总统套房 -
Yeah, it's the presidential suite.
副总统吧
Vice presidential, anyway.
听着 我看了你的支持率数字
Listen, I've seen the disapproval numbers.
所以我明白这里的微妙局势
So I appreciate the delicate situation here.
呃 只是工作的一部分而已
Uh, just part of the job.
不 不是的 这是Will
No, it's not. This is Will.
Will 他们对支持率的评价是什么?
Will, what were they saying about the disapproval?
对不起 女士 网上都写的是菊花被完爆
Apologies, ma'am. Effed in the b-hole across all networks.
女士 这可是挥之不去的画面感 我跟你说
Ma'am, that is a lingering image to try to overcome, I'll tell you.
这是什么意思 众议员?
What's this about, congressman?
呃 我是希望...女士...我们能谈谈
Well, I was hoping maybe, ma'am, we could have a moment.
好吧 你坐  谢谢
Yes. have a seat.  Thank you.
女士 我不希望你这次为我竞选州长背书
Ma'am, I don't want you to endorse my run for governor at this time.
呃 Roger
Um, well, Roger,
这个对我很难...  嗯哼
that is difficult...  Mm-hmm.
我都已经到这里来了
For me because I'm here.
是的 这很好 能给我来点水吗?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, that's great. Can I get some water?
对我来说...
Um, it's being put to me...
Gary 能给我来点水吗?  好的
Gary, can I get some water?  Yeah.
对我来说...我很抱歉...
It's being put to me that... and I apologize...
但是从政治角度而言 你就是残次品啊
but politically speaking, you are damaged goods.
我听说你的信用已经降到了...
I'm hearing that your credibility is...
降到哪了来着 Will?  马桶里
Where is it located, Will?  The toilet.
嗯哼 不是我的话哈
Mm-hmm. Again, not my words.
所以...  马桶里?
so...  The toilet?
我不要这个  好的
I don't want this.  Okay.
更确切的说 是上大号的地方  你是谁?
More accurately, the crapper.  Who are you?
这个菜鸟他妈是谁?  谁也不是
Who is this fucking infant?  No one.
我跟你说清楚 Roger
Let me be very clear with you about something, okay, Roger?
我都不喜欢你
I don't even like you.
对  对吧?
right.  Right?
现在我...被告知要来为你背书
And now I'm, you know, been told to come here and endorse you.
所以你明白会有多尴尬吗?
So do you understand how embarrassing
我现在如果不给你背书的话
this would be for me now not to endorse you?
是的 当然 我明白
Yes, of course. I get it, yeah.
听着 女士 本着互惠精神而言
And listen, in the spirit of reciprocity, ma'am,
我个人也不是很在乎你
I don't really care for you much either personally.
你不能阻止我给你背书
You can't stop me from endorsing you.
那我就公开拒绝你的支持 -
Then I will reject the endorsement publically.
副总统女士 你要休息五分钟吗?
Madam Vice President, do you need five minutes?
不 我不用休息五分钟
No, I don't need five minutes.
我他妈好得不得了
I'm absolutely fucking fine.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
Roger 你会不会有时候想到
You know, Roger, do you sometimes think about,
我给你这个 你给我那个
I don't know, I give you this and you give me that
然后黑的上来 棕的下去什么的?
and black is up, but brown is down now?
你明白我的意思么?  嗯哼
do you know What I mean?  Mm-hmm.
在生活中或者说仅是出于爱
I mean, in life or even just with love,
我是说 归根结底
you know, I mean, at the end of the day,
难道我们不都是...人么?
you know, aren't we just all finally just, you know, people?
说得对 女士  是的
True words, ma'am.  Yeah.
你知道吗 我已经...
I mean, you know, I haven't...
我已经有...三个月
I haven't seen my... my daughter
没见过我女儿了
in, like, three months.
而Ted就...哇!
And Ted is just, you know, whaa!
我不知道他去了哪 你知道吗?
I don't know where he went, you know?
而我...
You know, and I would...
我很想去参加那场派对 你知道吗?
I would love to go to that party, you know?
我想到处都去
I would like to be everywhere.
听着 副总统女士 我很抱歉
Look, Madam Vice President, I'm sorry.
我一点也不为此高兴 -
This doesn't give me any pleasure.
不许说你没有高兴
Don't you say it gives you no pleasure.
任何人说这句话的意思
When anybody ever says that,
都是他们都特高兴
all they mean is that it does give them so much pleasure.
听着...  我知道那是什么意思
Look...  I know What that means.
也许你应该来一下 好吗?
Maybe you should make an address, okay?
说一些政治啊美国人团结起来啊之类的
Talk about politics and America working together.
我他妈知道怎么演讲
I know how to give a motherfucking speech.
不许用你没有的下巴来戳我
Don't you patronize me with your no jaw.
你个没下巴的众议员
You congressman no jaw.
好了 女士 我们该...我们必须走了
Okay, ma'am. We should... we have to go.
都他妈滚  好的 好的
Get The Fuck out.  Okay. Okay.
他不是个好人
He was just not a nice man.
我去给你泡杯茶 好吗?
I'll get you some tea, okay?
我把Mike留下来 他可以留这里陪你
I'll just leave Mike. He can stay here with you.
非常抱歉你流了眼泪  是的
I'm sorry about your tears.  Yeah.
太逊了
They suck.
我爸爸曾经说过
You know, my papaw used to say,
暴风雨之前都会很黑暗的 所以...
it's always darkest before the storm. So...
噢 是黎明 是黎明之前
Oh, the dawn, the dawn.
黎明之前总是最黑暗的  然后他就会亲我
It's always darkest before the dawn. And then he would kiss me.
好了 这个听起来可能有点疯狂 不过就这么办吧
All right, this might sound crazy, but go with it.
她哭得很真实
Her crying was very authentic
而且很人性化
and humanizing.
好吧
Okay.
我喜欢你的想法
I like your thinking.
我其实觉得还有一点让人性致勃发 -
I actually found it slightly erotic, too.
我收回刚才的话
I take it back.
所以我才花了这么久才和Angie分手的
That's why it took me so long to split up with Angie.
她老是哭 我就老是硬
She'd always cry, I'd always get a hard-on.
现在我被你绕晕了  听着
Now you've lost me.  Listen.
我们得商量一下这个
We should spitball on this, though.
玩哭泣大法
The crying game play, all right?
我们只需要设计她一下 然后让摄像机转起来
All we've got to do is set her up and let the cameras roll.
然后我们就捅她的泪点
Then we've just got to tweak the tear nipple.
我们怎么实施?
How do we make it happen?
可以朝她喷胡椒喷雾
Could spray her with pepper spray.
说她胖 开玩笑的
Call her fat. Kidding.
什么把她弄哭的?
What is it that made her cry?
是Catherine 对吧?
It's Catherine, right?
缺席母亲的刺痛
The absent mother blubber.
天才啊  对
Genius.  Yeah.
中式女儿的折磨 这个很不错 -
Chinese daughter torture. It's a good one.
天哪 我不相信我们在做这个了
God, I can't believe we're doing this.
另一方面来说 我们现在是在
On the other hand, we are currently polling lower than a side of beef
画了眼睛的牛肉旁边密谋 所以...
with eyes drawn on it, so...
好了 女士 又淡泡泡又多 好吗?  是的
Okay, ma'am, light and frothy.  Yeah.
卡普奇诺政治 好吗? 俄亥俄的三大产业是...
Cappuccino politics, okay? Big three industries in Ohio...
橡胶  石化 农业  对的 好
Rubber, petrochemical, agriculture.  Right. Okay.
使劲说橡胶 这是个大橡胶州  好的 没问题
Hit rubber. It's a big rubber state.  Okay. Good. Yeah.
那是什么? 传真件么? 还是你1988年写给自己的留言?
What is that, a fax? Is that a message to yourself from 1988?
你看是谁在和总统打高尔夫
Look who's playing golf with the president.
Danny Chung.
Chung  闭嘴
Chung.  Shut up.
那是什么?  别担心
What is that?  Don't worry about it.
Felicia 等一下 你尽管问她女儿的事 好吗?
Felicia, one second. Feel free to dive right in on the daughter, okay?
因为我们希望你问支持率的问题
'Cause we want to hit these disapproval ratings head on.
看吧 他对我这么说话的时候 我就觉得很紧张
See, when he says things like that to me, it makes me anxious.
我们刚知道Chung州长在和总统打高尔夫
We just found out that Governor Chung is golfing with potus.
所以如果你想提这个话头的话...  好的
So, if you want to talk about that...  All right.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
能回俄亥俄州来真棒
It is just great to be back in the state of Ohio.
最近这几个月你很不顺吧
Been a rough couple of months for you, though.
你的阻挠改革停滞不前
Your filibuster reform stalled.
绿色产业倡议也死了
Clean jobs initiative, dead in the water.
你说了很多希望带来改变的话
You talk a lot about really wanting to be able to make change.
你还觉得自己可以改变什么吗?
Do you still think you're gonna be able to make that happen?
当然了 是的 我为我们感到非常自豪
Oh, absolutely. Yeah, I'm very proud
对于目前的成就
of what we've been able to achieve thus far.
那你感觉自己是重回游戏了么? -
So you feel you're back in the game?
呃 这对我来说可不是游戏
Well, it's not a game to me.
而且流言肯定也让你很受伤
Must be very hurtful for you, too, with all the gossip going around.
到底她会下台么? 我才知道
Is she gonna go? I just understand today
今天总统和Chung州长打高尔夫了
that the president is golfing with Governor Chung.
这个消息困扰到你了吗?
Does that bother you?
总统
Well, I mean, the president
想和谁打高尔夫都行
can play golf with whoever he likes.
可我来这里是因为我有工作要做
But I'm here because I have work to do.
这是全年无休的 这是我的政治职责
It's 24/7. It's a public duty.
全年无休那就是说没有多少时间 留给你的家人了?
24/7 doesn't leave you much time for your family,
你女儿
your daughter...
呃 这是一个让人精疲力尽的日程 确实是这样
Well, I mean, it's a punishing schedule, that's for sure.
我是说 你会...你会累
I mean, you get... you get tired
而且会被...被打击
and you get knocked... knocked back.
但是...
But...
你能想象吗 Felicia
Can you imagine, Felicia,
如果我累了的话
if I'm tired,
想象一下俄亥俄州的橡胶工人有多累吧
imagine how tired the rubber makers are here in Ohio.
她太牛逼了
She is magnificent.
日复一日的制作橡胶
Making rubber day in and day out.
我觉得俄亥俄就是橡胶球之州
I feel that Ohio is the rubber ball state,
如果你仔细想想的话 它永远都会反弹回来
if you think about it.
俄亥俄公民民主党筹款会
Always bouncing back.
我不知道她到底在想什么
I don't know what the hell she could have been thinking.
你上一次一天哭两回是什么时候?
When was the last time you cried twice in one day?
比你想的要近多了
It was a little more recently than you'd think.
Oddjob (007中的一个反派)
Oddjob.
过来 你老板他妈是搞什么?
Come here. What the fuck gives with your boss?
我看见她崩溃了
I saw the meltdown.
众议员 我看到的是热情和信念
Congressman, I saw passion. I saw conviction.
我看到的是他妈疯婆子
I saw a fucking crazy lady. That's what I saw.
如果她提到我名字的话 如果我得到了支持的话
If she mentions my name, if I get the stamp of approval,
要是她点石成屎的手敢懂我一下 我就冲着你来 朋友
the midas touch from Jenny shitfinger, I'm coming for you, pal.
我和美利坚国会会弄死你的 -
Me and the congress of the United States will get your ass.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
去问问你的朋友Macauley 也许他能帮助你
Ask your buddy Macauley about it. Maybe he can help you.
有请副总统
The vice president.
你好! 是的 我看见你了
Hello! Yes. I see you.
看看这些人啊
Oh, wow, look at this group.
他们能在我之后活到投票的那天么?
Are they gonna live long enough to make it to election day,
也许不会
right behind me? Probably not.
哈罗啊 不能投票的娃娃们
Hello, children who do not vote.
访谈的回馈很好
We're getting great media response to the interview.
你也收到了吗?  不 更好
Are you getting this, too?  No, better.
我在这房间里已经调查过了 很热情 很友好
I've been polling the room. It's warm, it's friendly.
如果这在俄亥俄管用 那全国都会买账的
If this plays in Ohio, it's gonna go national.
来吧 Amy
Come on, Amy.
Marcus  什么?
Marcus.  What?
我做了一个蛋糕 上面有你的脸
I made you a cake with your face on it.
不是吧? 噢!
Are you kidding me? Oh!
那看起来就像是我在参议院 度过了漫长一天的样子
That looks like me after a long day in the Senate.
我想她就捐了50块 -
I think she's only paid 50 bucks.
我得走了
I have to go.
副总统女士  什么?
Madam Vice President.  Yes?
我要给你介绍一位真正的白金捐赠者
I'd like to introduce you to one of our actual platinum donors.
我有一些关于税改的想法想和你聊聊
I have some great ideas about tax reform I want to talk to you about.
我很想听  呃 这世上有两种人
I want to hear them.  Well, there's two types of people.
啊哈  对吧? 有一种是抓取者
Uh-huh.  Okay? you got grabbers.
然后是另一种
And then you have the other kind.
我没有给他们取名字 他们不抓东西
I don't have a name for that. The ones who don't grab.
抓取者 好吧
Oh.  The grabbers, right,
他们抓住世界的蛋蛋 好吗?
they take the world by the scrotum, okay?  Oh.
而他们让事件发生  这个口味太重了
And they make It happen.  this is just riveting stuff.
噢 对不起 对不起  什么?
Oh, I'm so sorry. So sorry.  Yes?
我不知道要说什么 所以我就只好对你耳语了
I don't know what to say, so I'm just whispering instead.
我这里有...
Oh, I have the...
中东的问题  你一会儿再说吧
Middle east.  you Can talk later.
我们还有一晚上呢  很感激 你好
We have All night.  I appreciate that. Hello. Uh-huh.
我只是想离
I just want to eat in a quiet corner
这帮二货远远的
away from these bozos, okay?
找个安静的角落自己吃东西 好吗?
And that's the essence of a grabber.
这就是抓取者的精髓
Okay?  Mm-hmm.
对吧?  嗯哼
You'd think with all the money I'm jerking up the wall here,
你以为就凭我射在墙上的这些钱
I'd get more than a stuffed chicken breast.
我吃得会比夹心鸡胸肉强
Right, well, you know, I've got to tell you,
就是 我告诉你吧 这些承包伙食的啊...
these caterers, they've got...
我捐了3万块 就换了一块鸡胸肉
I gave 30,000 bucks, I get a chicken breast.
那个人连500块也没捐 他也得了一块鸡胸肉
That guy didn't give 500 bucks, he's got a chicken breast.
那我得的是什么 馅料么?  嗯哼
What do I get, stuffing?  Mm-hmm.
好吧  给我来个鸡腿什么的啊
Okay.  Throw me a drumstick or something.
Larry  你好啊
Larry.  Hey.
真高兴见到你  为啥 你惹上官司了?
It's good to see you.  Why, you need a lawyer?
好吧 听着是这么回事儿
All right, look. Listen.
我可能惹上了点儿麻烦
I may have gotten involved in a little something.
要是我被国会委员会质询了怎么办
What happens if I get called in before a congressional committee?
这样的话 你需要准备三个说辞
Okay, you need three versions of your statement.
类似我自己的版本 对方的版本 还有真实版本是吧?
Uh-huh, like what I say happened, what they say happened, and the truth?
没错吧?
Right?
书面的 口头的 和一份简短的口头版本
A written, an oral, and a shorter oral
有的时候会有时间限制  好吧
in case of a time limit.  right.
国会委员会问问题你当然得说真话 Dan
Yeah, you want to tell a congressional committee the truth, Dan.
出点儿什么差错 你就会因作伪证被起诉
Anything out of line, you're looking at a perjury charge.
奶奶的! -
Fuck!
别给自己惹麻烦 听见没?
Don't call attention to yourself, all right?
就低调点儿小心行事
Just lay low, keep your head down.
好吧 那如果真的发生了
All right, now let's say this does actually happen
我被叫去质询 那是个什么情况啊
and I get called in, what's it like up there?
你想像一下做梦梦见橄榄球队教练冲你发飙
You know those dreams where your football coach is screaming at you,
你就低着头 还穿的跟秀兰邓波尔似的 接下来就被打得就满地找牙了 想象得出不
you look down, you're dressed like Shirley Temple and then all your teeth fall out?
这个跟国会委员会比起来 简直是梦幻迪士尼
That's like a Disney version of a congressional committee.
你会经历各类问题 可能是温和的 也可能是严厉的拷问
You're gonna get hometown, downtown questions.
甚至遭到党派攻击 因为有人一定会哗众取宠
You'll catch partisan shit. There's gonna be grandstanding.
然后一旦他们尝到了甜头 他们就会觉得你不行了
And if they smell blood, if they think that you're going down
然后大肆攻击
and there's gonna be a kill,
你搞不好还会被鞭尸
you might get what we call corpse fucking.
老天爷啊 鞭尸?
Jesus. Corpse fucking?
就是就算你已经倒了 他们还会喋喋不休地攻击你
That's what it's called where they take your mortal remains
并且乐在其中
and have as much fun with it as they can.
因为人人都想上电视 懂不?
'Cause everybody wants to be the guy getting the TV sound bite, okay?
他们会一直谈论你
And they're gonna be talking about you.
懂了  好的
Yeah.  Yeah.
谢谢你们
Thank you so much.
衷心感谢大家 各位晚上好
Thank you so, so, very, very much. Good evening, everyone.
你干嘛呢? -
What are you doing?
先生 这个流泪戏码大家很买账啊
Sir, this crying is tracking pretty well.
你说啥?
What?
哎呀妈啊  没错
Oh, shit.  Yeah, it's good.
这下大洗牌了 -
Okay, that changes everything.
她是一位你们都十分熟悉的人
She's someone I know you know very well.
快过来  放松点儿 行不?
Hey, come here.  Relax, okay?
我跟她谈过了 你们也谈过了
I spoke to her. You spoke to her.
她不可能背书支持你的
She's not gonna fucking endorse.
不 不 不 她必须现在就背书
No, no, no. We want her to endorse now.
听懂没? 她已经从人人嫌变成人人爱了
Okay? She's gone from toxic to turn-on.
反正就等我们一点头 你就跟她放话 听懂没
So just... when we give you the nod, give her the signal, all right?
你俩现在搞得我胃灼热了都
You guys are burning a fucking hole through my stomach.
我花了一下午时间按照你俩意思来
I just spent all afternoon fixing this for you.
结果现在可又不玩儿了?  你头一回遇到么?
Now you want me to unfix it?  is this your first day in The game?
我看他好像快说完了...
I think he's wrapping up, so...
好吧  你感觉如何?
Okay.  How you feeling?
这样啊 我是个政治上的麻风病人 情感上的定时炸弹
Well, I'm a political leper, and I'm an emotional time bomb.
所以你猜怎么着... 咱上台吧
So here's an idea... let's put me onstage.
Selina Meyer.
女士们先生们 谢谢各位
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you so much.
太美妙了 谢谢各位
So wonderful. Thank you.
请入座 谢谢各位 这是我...
Please be seated. Thank you so much. It is my very...
快点儿 你等啥呢? 快点儿给信号
Come on, what are you waiting for? Give her the signal.
啥信号啊?
What the fuck is the signal?
哪有什么国际通用的信号 能表达'快背书'的意思?
There's no international signal to endorse.
你他妈动点儿脑子啊 竖个大拇指啥的
Use your fucking head. Give her a thumbs up or something.
我的天啊 今天真是
Oh, my goodness. Well, this has been
非比寻常 不是吗?
quite the day, hasn't it?
我们爱你
We love you!
谢谢你们 -
Thank you very much.
她可不能一天哭三回
She can't cry three times in a day.
三振就出局了 -
That's three strikes and you're out.
她的泪腺有多发达啊?
How big are her tear ducts?
跟他妈潮汐似的一阵一阵的涌 -
It's like they're fucking tidal.
在这样开心的场合...
Such a happy occasion, and...
老天爷啊 我去 别背书了
Jesus Christ. Fuck it, don't endorse.
我非常荣幸能来到联邦第17个州
I'm so glad to be here in the 17th state of the union.
我的祖父来自辛辛那提
My grandfather, he was from Cincinnati, as a matter of fact.
Oh.
我家过去常说这么一句话
We used to have a saying in our family.
我们常说不喜欢自己的
We used to say we're awfully embarrassed
犬牙形象
by our buckteeth.
但是来自俄亥俄州 我自豪
But we were mighty proud of our buckeyes.
好了 背书 快背书
Okay, endorse. Endorse. Endorse.
你确定?  背书 快点儿
You're sure?  Endorse. Yes.
我...
I, um...
仍然想念我的祖父
I still miss my grandpa.
干嘛呢 大力水手?
What is that, Popeye?
不是 让她坚强起来  他太了不起了
No, be strong.  He was the best.
他... 他无比坚强
He was... he was such a strong man
因为他来自一个伟大的州
from a great state.
这就是我今天来这儿的原因
And so that's why I've come here today.
我来这里
I've come here today
是为了支持
to give my 100% support
Roger Furlong众议员
to congressman Roger Furlong
成为下一任
to be the next, the best,
俄亥俄州州长
governor of Ohio.
没错
That's right.
就是你 快上来
That's you. Come on up here.
什么情况这是?
What the hell just happened?
跟你共襄盛举真是荣幸啊
So great to be part of your feel-good moment.
你个下作的混蛋
You're a dirty little prick.
天啊 真心谢谢你
Oh, boy. Thank you so much.
那是必须  天啊
Absolutely.  Oh, boy.
别忘了你的儿童增高椅 -
Don't forget your booster seat.
那就别占着
Oh, shove it up your ass.
谢谢你  好的
Thanks So much.  Okay.
那个会读唇语的记者没来吧? -
Hey, that photographer who reads lips,
没有
he's not here, is he?  Mm-mmm.
没来啊 这下放心了
No. That's a blessing.
你看芝加哥先驱论坛报没?
Did you see the Chicago Tribune?
哦 好极了 我从来没这么喜欢看报纸过
Oh, this is so great. I've never enjoyed reading this much.
知道么 我妈说Selina看起来 闪耀着脆弱的人性光芒
You know, my mom said that Selina looked human and vulnerable.
好啊  这可不是赞美
Great.  Not a compliment.
她认为脆弱是人性的弱点
She sees human vulnerability as a weakness.
我喜欢你妈  说的可是我妈啊 Dan
I like your mom.  Don't talk about my mother, Dan.
早!  你看芝加哥先驱论坛报没?
Good morning!  Did you see the Chicago Tribune?
看见了 看过了 消化了
I've seen it, I've read it, I've eaten it,
我沐浴在成功的氛围里  如今我回来啦 姑娘小伙儿们
I've showered in it. I'm back, my babies.
是啊 跟橡胶上帝似的
Yeah, you are. Like rubber Jesus.
Dan 快过来跟我握握手啊
And, Dan, get over here and shake my hand.
干得多漂亮啊  我很荣幸
What a Great job you did.  my pleasure.
说真的 让我支持Furlong
Seriously, getting me to endorse Furlong.
大家还不掌声鼓励一下?
How about that round of applause?
快点儿啊 大家鼓掌
Come on, guys. Give it up for him.
真棒
Absolutely great.
你知道这些人里没一个真心喜欢你的吧 -
You know none of these people generally like you.
谁会在乎啊?
So fucking what?
大家好 哎呀这么隆重!
Hey, everyone. Oh, hey!
是呀 也是时候了 谢谢
Hey, it's about time. Thank you.
你好 Mike
Hey, Mike.
总统先生对事态的新发展很满意
Potus is so excited about this new narrative.
我设法让Selina在电视上哭出来了
I engineered Selina crying on camera.
我就是木偶大师 匹诺曹
I'm the puppet master. I'm Pinocchio.
匹诺曹不是大师 Mike 他就是个木偶
Pinocchio wasn't the puppet master, Mike. He was the puppet.
哦对  五岁娃娃都知道
Uh, yeah, he was.  Five-year-olds get that.
Jonah 男士俱乐部有啥指示?
Jonah, do you come bearing news from the gentleman's club?
我是来表达总统的支持的
I come bearing a message of support from the president.
总统先生打电话了 -
Oh.  As you know, he called.
Sue 他打了么?
Sue, did the president call?
没有  哎呦
No.  huh.
这样的 不是真正意义上的电话
Well, it wasn't an actual call.
是让我来传达一个电话的意思  嗯
I am Here in lieu of that call.  Uh-huh.
他跟我...  我有一个重大消息要宣布
But he And We are...  I have a very big announcement to make.
请大家跟我进办公室
I'd like everyone to follow me into my office, please.
这边请 嗯 我是想
This-a-way. Okay, so I am about to announce
进行一项改组
a certain realignment.
Mike 真遗憾呐
Oh, Mike. I am sorry for your loss.
Dan 你升职了
Dan, you're getting a promotion.
Wow. Yeah!
太谢谢你了  不用客气
Thank you so much.  You're welcome.
我刚签了份租车合同 如果我能再多呆半年...
I just signed for an auto lease. If I could get six months...
以后我每天的对外反驳都由你来负责好吗
I want you to be in charge of day-to-day rebuttal for me, all right?
政策和公共演讲方面以后由你负责
You'll be the new director of policy and presentation.
谢谢你 这就是我毕生所求啊
Thank you, ma'am. This is all I've ever wanted.
这是我毕生不屑的 -
This is all I've never wanted.
他现在成我上司了?
Is he... is Dan my boss now?
我能评论一句不 这太精彩了?
Can I just say that this is really exciting to watch?
我想我有活儿要干了
I guess I've got some business to attend to.
啥活儿啊?  你不需要知道Mike
What business?  That's a need-to-know basis, Mike,
这种信息不对你开放
and you don't have the clearance.
真好笑 真的假的?
Funny. Is that true?
真可悲 你就跟
This is sad. You're like an old panda
公园里快被结果的大熊猫一样啊
that's gonna get put down at the zoo.
还能阖家观赏呢  滚蛋
they bring kids in to watch that.  Fuck off.
我猜我安全吧
I'm assuming I'm safe.
Amy 你为了我假装流产
Amy, you pretended to have a miscarriage for me.
你仍然是我队伍中不可或缺的一员
You remain crucial to my policy team.
听好了 姑娘小伙儿 我升职了
All right, boys and girls, I got a promotion.
第一件事就是先发一份媒体声明
So first order of business is to issue a press release,
内容我已经写好了
which I already have written.
Colette 给你个机会
Colette, if you would do the honors.
在我的文件夹第一段里
In the me file under phase one.
好了 你俩
Okay, and you and you,
搬这张桌子
I need you to move this desk.
动作快 别给我摆一张苦逼孤儿脸
Let's go. Don't give me that sad orphan face.
把你的零食袋子和你的水瓶子带好 赶紧滚出来
Take your little snack pack and your water bottle and get the fuck out.
听着 Dan  咋了?
Hey, Dan.  Yes?
恭喜升职了 咱俩有空喝一杯去
Congrats on the big promotion. You and I should grab another drink.
你猜怎么的? 跟我秘书Mike说一声
You know what? Run it by my secretary. His name is Mike.
不行不行 你得搬回去
No, no, no, you've got to move that back.
我可不准你盯着我一整天
I'm not gonna have you eyeballing me all day.
不准他搬到那儿去  放松点儿 牛眼娃
That's not gonna go there.  Relax, cow eyes.
我才不会坐在这儿
I'm not gonna be sitting here looking at your...
一直盯着你的牛眼看呢 凳子放这儿
cow eyes the whole time. Guys, seat goes right here.
糟了  咋了?咋了? 啥事儿?
Shit, shit.  What? What? What?
推特上的新闻 副总统火了
Twitter eruption. Veep's trending.
Amy 什么情况?  你火了 夫人
Amy, what's going on?  Um, you're trending, ma'am.
我也在推特上 但是他老让我重新申请账号
I'm on Twitter, but it wants me to create a new account.
我不知道咋申请  申就是了
I don't know how to do that.  Well, then do that.
Amy 怎么了? 怎么回事儿Amy?
Amy, what the fuck? What is it, Amy?
俄亥俄的一个记者Felicia
This is the reporter from Ohio, Felicia.
等会儿 等会儿 我知道了
Wait, wait. No, I got it.
被副总统的团队耍的团团转
Got played by team veep.
她们让我想办法逼她哭出来
They wanted me to make her cry.
井号键爱哭又虚伪的副总统 这他么怎么回事儿?
Hashtag FakeVeepWeep. What the fuck?
啥? 谁想让我哭? -
What? Who wanted to make me cry?
Mike让你哭出来的
Mike engineered your crying, ma'am.
他说他是你的木偶大师
He said that he was your puppet master.
他说他是你的匹诺曹
Actually, he said he was your Pinocchio,
但我猜他要说的是盖比特 那才是木偶师傅
but I think he meant Geppetto, who was actually the puppet master.
Mike设法让你在镜头前面哭的
Mike got you to cry on camera.
搞什么 Mike?  搞什么Mike?
What the fuck, Mike?  What the fuck, Mike?
Amy去我办公室 Mike特别是你
Amy, get into my office. Mike, especially you.
进我办公室 好的
Go into my office. Okay.
老天啊 看这位的块头
Holy Christ. Look at the size of this one.
哥们儿我猜你跟我这位同性恋小矮人儿差不多高
Buddy, I think you're as big as my gay dwarf.
我现在要见副总统
I need to see the vice president now.
抱歉我不在这儿工作 我确实在为西部工作...
Sorry, I don't work here. I do work in the West...
那赶紧闪开啊 你这哪儿的斜塔...
Well, then get the hell out of my way, you leaning tower of...
比萨斜塔  不是
Pisa.  No.
粑粑斜塔?  没错
Shit?  Good.
赶紧的  好的先生
Move it.  Yes, sir.
小心肝儿 我要见副总统
Hey, sweet cakes. I need to get in to see the veep.
议员 你再这么叫我一次 我就送你去急诊室
Congressman, if you call me that again, you'll need to see a paramedic.
交给你了  等会儿 等会儿!
Take care of that.  Whoa, whoa, whoa!
混蛋 你在干嘛?  你以为我是个爱哭鬼么?
Big bully, what are you doing?  You think I'm a crybaby?
抱歉叨扰 副总统女士
Sorry to barge in, Madam Vice President.
是么 Larry 听着 Furlong在我办公室里
Yeah, Larry, listen. Furlong is in the office.
别跟Furlong说话 你要保持低调
Don't talk to Furlong. You need to keep a low profile.
我刚发了一份媒体声明说我升职了
I just issued a press release announcing my promotion.
再见吧 Dan
Bye, Dan.
说实话 女士 我很生气 Wil 跟她解释一下
Frankly, ma'am, I'm angry. Will, tell her why.
媒体说你刻意演哭戏
The press claims that you intentionally cried
为的是掩盖
in order to divert attention away from the fact
我们强迫群众参与募捐会这个事实
that we had to bus people into the fundraiser.
现在我不想被你这些谎言牵连
And now I'm being implicated in your disgusting little lies,
而且说句实在的 我可不愿意蹚你这浑水
and, actually, I don't feel like being dragged into the toilet with you, ma'am.
首先 议员先生
Number one, congressman,
我已经受够你这些屁话了
I'm sick of taking your shit, okay?
其次 第一条再次强调一遍
Number two, number one again.
哭是演出来的 我是被操纵的
The crying was manipulated, ma'am. I was manipulated.
这个会议也该截止了
And this meeting is now terminated
因为这压根儿就不应该被提上日程
because this was never a meeting to even begin with.
你该走了
You're gonna need to leave 'cause I'm not really aware
要不我不客气了
of where my actions will take me, okay?
你干嘛? 用内裤勒死我?
What are you gonna do? You gonna choke me with some spanx?
你想试试?
Do you want to try me?
你包里有口气清新剂没? 走吧
You got breath mints in that bag? Let's go.
你眉心有个红点啊 Danno
Oh, you got a nice big red dot in the middle of your forehead, Danno.
你被瞄上了我告诉你  你说啥?
And it ain't a fucking bindi.  Excuse me?
你最好装备起来 牛仔 因为我要对这间办公室
You'd better saddle up, cowgirl, 'cause I'm gonna ride this whole office
展开国会调查听证
into a congressional investigative hearing
听证项目是Macauley修正案和纵容下属腐败 -
over the Macauley amendment and the attendant corruption.
放轻松
Just relax.
我觉得你应该去整一个头盔
I think you might want to get yourself a helmet, okay.
再加上个防弹背心和下体铁护身
And a bulletproof vest and an iron jockstrap.
因为我会找人爆你头 捅你背 让你蛋碎
'Cause you're gonna get your head shot, your back stabbed, and your nuts danced on.
周一愉快
Have a good Monday.
再见 Sue
Bye, Sue.
你暂时别升职了
All right, you're gonna need to stay in your former position.
好么? 保持低调
Okay? Keep a low profile.
瞧好了 Dan 爽!
In your face, Dan. Mmm!
我貌似已经发了一条新闻稿
Um, ma'am, I may have already issued a press release
关于我升职的  真的假的?
regarding my promotion.  Really?
那我能把你撤了不? 恐怕不行
Well, can I unpromote you? I don't think so.
他又成了我上司了? -
Is he my boss again?
头衔上是? 但你比他资深
Only in title, all right? You're still senior to him.
瞧好吧  够了?拜托 Mike
In your fucking face.  Stop it, okay? Please, Mike.
Dan 喝酒的事儿 再说了哈?
Hey, Dan, I'm gonna take a rain check on that beer, okay?
我滴神啊 这么着
Oh, my God in heaven. So, let's see.
我刚提的负责反驳的人选
The guy that I have just put in charge of rebutting
现在负责进行反驳
is now in charge of rebutting questions
就Macauley修正案问题
over the Macauley amendment,
如今看来是最不合适的人选
which is the very thing he should be nowhere near rebutting.
对吧?  我跟你提醒过的 夫人
Right?  I did warn you about him, ma'am.
好了 出去吧 Amy 快滚出去
Okay, get out, Amy. Get out of my office.
看见没 现在... 我真的要哭了
See, now... now I want to cry.
可欲哭无泪啊
But I can't cry.
能给我杯茶不?  好的
Can I Get you a cup of tea? Okay.  Yeah.
你懂不懂 这工作折磨死我了
You know, I mean, this job has fucked me up so bad.
我现在他妈连哭都哭不出来
Now I don't fucking know if I can cry anymore.
我可不担心这个 夫人
I wouldn't worry about it, ma'am.
我是说 你只用干四年 所以...
I mean, you've only got four years of this, so...
恐怕得8年 万一咱连任了呢
Eight years, I guess, if we got reelected,
很明显
obviously.
要竞选总统的话就是12年
12 if you run for president.
16年 总统再连任
16, two-term.
你想想
So think about that.
Egan 好吧? Dan Egan
Egan, all right? Dan Egan.
大写字母D的Dan
That's Dan with a capital D
然后他妈的听清了 Egan
and Egan with an open your fucking ears.
没错 耳朵的那个E
Yes, E as in ears.
好 我等着
Yeah, I'll hold.
Dan走人了以后把那桌子搬回来 成不?
When Dan goes home, I want that desk back here, okay?
不行 她很忙 明天也没空
No, she's busy. And tomorrow.
后天也不行
Well, that's tomorrow in the plural.
哪天都不行
All of them.